Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files C
    - Carter, Betty (Box A-22, Folder 102)
      Also one halftone print. Also two velox prints. Also one newspaper clipping that fell of the verso of a print.
    - Carter, Boysie (Box A-22, Folder 103)
    - Carter, Brent (Box A-22, Folder 104)
    - Carter, Calvin (Box A-22, Folder 105)
      Photographer if identified: Polk's Studio, City of New York/Department of Sanitation
    - Carter, Candace (Box A-22, Folder 106)
    - Carter, Carol D. (Box A-22, Folder 107)
    - Carter, Carol P. (and husband) (Box A-22, Folder 108)
    - Carter, Carolyn D. (Box A-22, Folder 109)
    - Carter, Charles (Box A-22, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: David J. Sullivan/Negro Market Organization
    - Carter, Charles A. (Box A-22, Folder 111)
    - Carter, Charles L. (Box A-22, Folder 112)
    - Carter, Charlie (Box A-22, Folder 113)
    - Carter, Chester (Box A-22, Folder 114)
      One print and one caption adhered to a large piece of lightweight paper. Both prints are badly darkened.
    - Carter, T.K. (Box A-22, Folder 115)
      One print of T.K. Carter. Also two other prints with seemingly-unrelated subjects.
    - Carter, Chuck (Box A-22, Folder 116)
    - Carter, Clarence (Box A-22, Folder 117)
    - Carter Community African Methodist Episcopal Church (Box A-22, Folder 118)
      Photographer if identified: G&W Photos
    - Carter, Dick (Box A-22, Folder 119)
    - Carter, Dona S. (Box A-22, Folder 120)
    - Carter, Dorothy (Box A-22, Folder 121)
    - Carter, Earle I. (Box A-22, Folder 122)
    - Carter, Edward A. (Sgt.) (Box A-22, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Signal Corps Photo.
    - Carter, Elmer (Box A-22, Folder 124)
      Note on folder: "See Inactive File"
    - Carter, Ernest (Box A-22, Folder 125)
    - Carter, Eunice Hunton (Attorney) (Box A-22, Folder 126)
    - Carter, Fleurette (Box A-22, Folder 127)
    - Carter, Floyd (Box A-22, Folder 128)
    - Carter, George (Box A-22, Folder 129)
    - Carter, Gloria (Box A-22, Folder 130)
    - Carter, Hank (Box A-22, Folder 131)
    - Carter, Harold (Box A-22, Folder 132)
    - Carter, Helen (Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 133)
    - Carter, Horace (Box A-22, Folder 134)
    - Carter, Howard (Box A-22, Folder 135)
    - Carter, Hurricane (Box A-22, Folder 136)
      See: Carter, Rubin "Hurricane"
    - Carter, James (Box A-22, Folder 137)
    - Carter, John (Box A-22, Folder 138)
    - Carter, Joy (Box A-22, Folder 139)
    - Carter, Joyce (Box A-22, Folder 140)
    - Carter, Julien (Rev.) (Box A-22, Folder 141)
      Photographer if identified: Hayes/L.I.P.P.A.
    - Carter, Larry (Box A-22, Folder 142)
    - Carter, Laura (Box A-22, Folder 143)
    - Carter, Lawrence A. (Box A-22, Folder 144)
    - Carter, Leonard H. (Box A-22, Folder 145)
    - Carter, Leroy E. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 146)
    - Carter, Lewis J. (Box A-22, Folder 147)
      Also one black and white negative of a halftone print.
    - Carter, Linwood (Box A-22, Folder 148)
      Also one velox print. Newspaper clipping adhered to verso of one print.
      Photographer if identified: President/Borough of Queens
    - Carter, Lisle (Box A-22, Folder 149)
      One print is badly darkened, printed on lightweight paper. Also one stereotype matrix. Also one halftone print.
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box A-22, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: The White House, Roy Lewis, Harris Photo, Dave Greene, David Kutz, Kwame Brathwaite, Ralph Cooper
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box A-22, Folder 151)
      Also one halftone print mounted on heavy board. One print has mylar and a typescript caption adhered to verso.
      Photographer if identified: The White House, Ralph Cooper, Bill Fitzpatrick/The White House, Kwame Brathwaite, United Press International
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box A-22, Folder 152)
      Also one velox print. Also one reproduction of an illustration. Also four loose press releases on five leaves total.
      Photographer if identified: The White House, David Kutz, Irving Newman, Xavier University of Louisiana, Harris Photo
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box A-22, Folder 153)
    - Carter, Lisle C. (and Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 154)
    - Carter, Margaret (Box A-22, Folder 155)
    - Carter, Marie (Box A-22, Folder 156)
    - Carter, Mary (Box A-22, Folder 157)
    - Carter-Smith, Mary (Box A-22, Folder 158)
    - Carter, Matthew A. (Box A-22, Folder 159)
    - Carter, Matthew G. (Box A-22, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: Master Studio Inc.
    - Carter, Nancy M. (Box A-22, Folder 161)
    - Carter, Nell (Box A-22, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: Bruce W. Stark, Juanita M. Cole
    - Carter, Pat (Box A-22, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: Jeff Kean
    - Carter, Penny (Box A-22, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, NYC Parks Recreation and Public Affairs Administration
    - Carter, Gwendolyn (Box A-22, Folder 165)
      Color print.
    - Carter, Randolph (Box A-22, Folder 166)
    - Carter, Ralph (Box A-22, Folder 167)
      Photographer if identified: WNBC-TV4, Martha Swope, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Carter, Regina (Box A-22, Folder 168)
    - Carter, Reginald (Box A-22, Folder 169)
      Photographer if identified: George M. West, B.F. Goodrich
    - Carter, Robert H. (Elder) (Box A-22, Folder 170)
    - Carter, Roland M. (Box A-22, Folder 171)
    - Carter, Rosemary (Box A-22, Folder 172)
    - Carter, Rowland (Box A-22, Folder 173)
    - Carter, Rozalind (Box A-22, Folder 174)
    - Carter, Rubin "Hurricane" (Box A-22, Folder 175)
    - Carter, Sara Lou (and family) (Box A-22, Folder 176)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Pictorial Enterprise, W.A. Knight
    - Carter, Shirley Varette (Box A-22, Folder 177)
    - Carter, Sylvester (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 178)
      Photographer if identified: Signal Corps Photo Lab/USMA West Point NY
    - Carter, Sylvester (Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 179)
    - Carter, Terry (Box A-22, Folder 180)
    - Carter, Thelma (Box A-22, Folder 181)
    - Carter, Thomas (Box A-22, Folder 182)
    - Carter, Tim (Box A-22, Folder 183)
    - Carter, Ulish (Box A-22, Folder 184)
    - Carter, Valerie (Box A-22, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: Conrad Waldinger, Emerich C. Gross
    - Carter, Ron (Box A-22, Folder 186)
    - Carter, Viola (Box A-22, Folder 187)
    - Carter, Weptunomah (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 188)
    - Carter, William A. (Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 189)
    - Carter, Woodard W. (Box A-22, Folder 190)
    - Carter, Woody (Box A-22, Folder 191)
    - Carter, Woodard (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Educational Services Incorporated/Ethiopia Training Program
    - Carter, Zachary W. (Box A-22, Folder 193)
    - Carter, Wilfred (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 194)
    - Carthan, Eddie James (Box A-22, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: Multi-Wester Public Relations, Lensman
    - Carthan, Wilma (Box A-22, Folder 196)
    - Cartlidge, A. Ray (Rev.) (Box A-22, Folder 197)
      Photographer if identified: Presbryterian Office of Information
    - Cartledge, Gregory (Box A-22, Folder 198)
    - Cartouche (Box A-22, Folder 199)
    - Cartwright, Bill (Box A-22, Folder 200)
    - Cartwright, Jim (Box A-22, Folder 201)
    - Cartwright, Jon (Box A-22, Folder 202)
      One print is in a small envelope.
    - Cartwright, Marguerite (Box A-22, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: John D. Schiff, Bert Smith
    - Cartwright, Roscoe E. (Box A-22, Folder 204)
    - Carty, Denise (Box A-22, Folder 205)
    - Carty, Leo (Box A-22, Folder 206)
    - Caruthers, Candace (Box A-22, Folder 207)
    - Caruthers, Sam (Box A-22, Folder 208)
    - Carver Democratic Club (Box A-22, Folder 209)
    - Carver Federal & Loan Bank (Box A-22, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Frank Silva, Milton McPhail, Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Kurt Brunson
    - Carver Federal & Loan Bank (Box A-22, Folder 211)
      Also one velox print. Also two paper stereotype matrices. Also one envelope containing five 4"x5" black and white negatives. Also a small envelope containing one strip of 2"x2" black and white film showing two frames. Some typescript paper and carbon press releases have ms. notations on them.
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, Dummett, Rapid News Service, Layne's Studio, James Gilbert/News Voice International, Ace Creative Services, Bro. David McAdams
    - Carver Federal & Loan Bank (Box A-22, Folder 212)
      Includes one group of approximately seven prints that are stuck together in a mass, paperclipped inside a loose leaf cover. Also one halftone print of article and photo. Also one approximately nine velox prints, including a stack of approximately eight that are stuck together.
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, A. Hansen, Milton McPhail, George West, Djordje Milicevic, Ace Creative Photos, James C. Campbell, Layne's Studio, Harris Photo
    - Cary, W. Sterling (Box A-22, Folder 213)
    - Casablanca (Box A-22, Folder 214)
    - Cascone, Jeanette L. (Box A-22, Folder 215)
    - Casdulan, Frenchie (Box A-22, Folder 216)
    - Caste - Live Revue (Box A-22, Folder 217)
      One print has a newspaper clipping adhered to verso.
    - Casey, Bernie (Box A-22, Folder 218)
    - Casey, Edmund C. (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 219)
    - Casey, Frank (Box A-22, Folder 220)
    - C.A.S.H. (Box A-22, Folder 221)
    - Cash, Alvin (Box A-22, Folder 222)
    - Cash, Johnny (Box A-22, Folder 223)
    - Cash, Rosalind (Box A-22, Folder 224)
      Also one velox print
    - Cashears (Box A-22, Folder 225)
    - Casher, Charlotte and Leslie (Box A-22, Folder 226)
    - Cashin, John (Dr.) (Box A-22, Folder 227)
    - Casimir, Camello (Box A-22, Folder 228)
    - Casley, Kate (Box A-22, Folder 229)
    - Caso, Ralph G. (Box A-22, Folder 230)
    - Cass, Carol (Box A-22, Folder 231)
    - Cass, James E. (Box A-22, Folder 232)
    - Cassady, Vivian (Box A-22, Folder 233)
    - Cassell, Alphonsus "Arrow" (Box A-22, Folder 234)
    - Cassell, Patricia (Mrs.) (Box A-22, Folder 235)
    - Caster, Richard (Box A-22, Folder 236)
    - Castillo, Gloria M. (Box A-22, Folder 237)
    - Castle, Lawrence (Box A-22, Folder 238)
      One clipping from a semigloss magazine page.
    - Castleberry, Ed (Box A-22, Folder 239)
    - Castleberry, Ed (Box A-22, Folder 240)
    - Castleberry, William (Box A-23, Folder 1)
    - Castor, Jimmy (Box A-23, Folder 2)
      6 velox prints. 2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints have typescript press release stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams, Fred Van Doren, Maurice Seymour, James J. Kriegsmann
    - Castor, Ruth L. (Box A-23, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: L. Kyle
    - Castro, Fidel (Box A-23, Folder 4)
    - Casual Classics (Box A-23, Folder 5)
    - "The Casuals" (Box A-23, Folder 6)
    - Catchings, L. Maynard Rev. (Box A-23, Folder 7)
      Also multiple typescript press releases.
      Photographer if identified: George B. Biggs
    - Catchings, L. Maynard Sr. & Mrs. (Box A-23, Folder 8)
      Photographer if identified: Methodist Prints by Toge Fujihira
    - Cates, Horace (Box A-23, Folder 9)
    - Catherwood, Martin (Box A-23, Folder 10)
    - Catlett, Octavia (Box A-23, Folder 11)
      Photographer if identified: Russ Carter
    - Catlett, Thurman (Box A-23, Folder 12)
    - Cato, Minto (Box A-23, Folder 13)
    - Cato, R. Milton (Box A-23, Folder 14)
    - Cato, Velma (Box A-23, Folder 15)
      Press release with halftone print.
    - Catoe, Clarence (Box A-23, Folder 16)
    - Cattle Prodder (Box A-23, Folder 17)
    - C.A.V. Enterprises (Box A-23, Folder 18)
      2 groups of 2 prints are stuck together with paste. 5 typescript memos from various NYC/NYS agencies, Mayor Beame.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Milton McPhail, Al Burley, Roy Stevens
    - C.A.V. Enterprises (Box A-23, Folder 19)
      1 print is line art.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Milton McPhail, Blackstone-Shelburne
    - The Cavaliers (Box A-23, Folder 20)
    - Cavanagh, Edward F. (Box A-23, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: Bakalar-Cosmo, G. Powell
    - Cave, Cito (Box A-23, Folder 22)
    - Cave, Claude Dr. (Box A-23, Folder 23)
    - Cave, Helene J. (Box A-23, Folder 24)
    - Cave, J. Ken (Box A-23, Folder 25)
    - Cave, Jill (Box A-23, Folder 26)
    - Cave, Vernal T. Dr. (Box A-23, Folder 27)
      Also one velox print and photocopied flier for "great musical therapy show for the shut-ins."
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bachrach, Dave Greene, Harris Photo, Hamilton Associates
    - Caviar (Box A-23, Folder 28)
    - Cawley, Dudley O. (Box A-23, Folder 29)
    - Canyon, Thomas H. (Box A-23, Folder 30)
    - Cazenave, Noel Dr. (Box A-23, Folder 31)
    - CBS Records (Box A-23, Folder 32)
    - Cearson, Vereda (Box A-23, Folder 33)
    - Ceasar, Adolph (Box A-23, Folder 34)
    - Ceasar, Roderick Bishop (Box A-23, Folder 35)
    - CEBA Awards (Box A-23, Folder 36)
    - Cedeno, Casar (Box A-23, Folder 37)
    - Celestial Choral (Box A-23, Folder 38)
    - The Celestics (Box A-23, Folder 39)
    - Celestin, Louis (Box A-23, Folder 40)
    - Cellar, Emanuel (Box A-23, Folder 41)
      2 typescript leaves.
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Cecil Layne, Ace Creative Photos, United Press International
    - Census (Box A-23, Folder 42)
      1980 census.
      Photographer if identified: Mark Mangold
    - Central Broadcasting Systems (Box A-23, Folder 43)
    - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council (Box A-23, Folder 44)
    - Central Line (Box A-23, Folder 45)
    - Central Park (Box A-23, Folder 46)
      Also press releases.
    - Central Park Joggers Trial (Box A-23, Folder 47)
    - Cepeda, Orlando (Box A-23, Folder 48)
      Photographer if identified: Robert W. Cottrol, United Press International, M Associates
    - Cephous, Milton A. Rev (Box A-23, Folder 49)
    - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men (Box A-23, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: Arnold Nelson, Bert Andrews,
    - CETA (Box A-23, Folder 51)
    - CeVara (Box A-23, Folder 52)
    - Chacon, Elio (Box A-23, Folder 53)
    - Chacon, Iris (Box A-23, Folder 54)
    - Chacon, Peter (Box A-23, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: Public Information Office, Parks Admin. (NYC)
    - Chadrich, Melvin (Box A-23, Folder 56)
    - "Chained" (Box A-23, Folder 57)
    - Chaka Ensemble (Box A-23, Folder 58)
    - Challenger, Rudy (Box A-23, Folder 59)
    - Chamber Dance Group (Box A-23, Folder 60)
    - Chamber Orchestra (Box A-23, Folder 61)
    - Chamberlin, Daniel; Chamberlin, David; Chamberlin, Wilt (Box A-23, Folder 62)
    - Chamberlin, Lee (Box A-23, Folder 63)
    - Chambers, Alexander (Rev.) (Box A-23, Folder 64)
    - Chambers, Lt. Andrew P. (Box A-23, Folder 65)
    - Chambers, Ben Rev. (Box A-23, Folder 66)
    - Chambers Brothers (Box A-23, Folder 67)
      2 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Werner J. Kuhn
    - Chambers, Curtis (Rev.) (Box A-23, Folder 68)
    - Chambers, Donna (Box A-23, Folder 69)
    - Chambers, Doris (Box A-23, Folder 70)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bro. David McAdams, Curt Clemons, Verna Photographers, George Hopkins
    - Floyd Chambers (Box A-23, Folder 71)
    - Chambers, Florence (Box A-23, Folder 72)
    - Chambers, Gene (Box A-23, Folder 73)
    - Chambers, Helen (Box A-23, Folder 74)
    - Chambers, Julius (Box A-23, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: Chrysler Photographic, Mobil Oil Corporation, James Gilbert, Pan American World Airways, Pictorial Enterprise, Cecil Layne
    - Chambers, Julius LeVonne (Box A-23, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: Bagwell, University of Pennsylvania
    - Chambers, Fr. Junius (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-23, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: TWA
    - Chambers, LaFawn (Box A-23, Folder 78)
      1 print is a Polaroid (coated).
    - Chambers, Lucille (Box A-23, Folder 79)
    - Chambers, Olga (Box A-23, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: "The News" (The Daily News)
    - Chambers, Theo (Box A-23, Folder 81)
    - Chambers, T. M. (Dr.), Chambers, Ted (Box A-23, Folder 82)
      One photo is of ballplayer Ted Chambers.
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Laughead Photographers, James Gilbert
    - Chambers, Wally (Box A-23, Folder 83)
    - Chambers, Yolande H. (Box A-23, Folder 84)
    - Chamblee, Anna (Box A-23, Folder 85)
    - Chamblee, Edee (Box A-23, Folder 86)
      Single-leaf career highlights sheet.
    - Chamblie, Edward (Mrs.) (Box A-23, Folder 87)
    - Chambliss, Chris (Box A-23, Folder 88)
      1 print is autographed. Also one velox print.
    - Champagne, Eugene (Box A-23, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: P.L. Gould
    - Champion, Jackson R. (Box A-23, Folder 90)
    - Chan, Buck (Box A-23, Folder 90)
    - Chan, Tahi (Box A-23, Folder 91)
    - Chance, Bob (Box A-23, Folder 92)
    - Chance, Boston (Box A-23, Folder 93)
    - Chance, Lucille (Box A-23, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Dianora Niccolini
    - Chance, Sonny (Box A-23, Folder 95)
    - Chance, Tom (Box A-23, Folder 96)
      Photographer if identified: Marty Cobin
    - Chance, William (Box A-23, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert, Cecil Layne
    - Chancellor, Sharon L. (Box A-23, Folder 98)
    - Chancey, Harrell (Box A-23, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Rhoden Photo and Press Service
    - Chandler, Gene (Box A-23, Folder 100)
      Photographer if identified: Geddes
    - Chandler, Gladstone (Box A-23, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Joshua L. Smith
    - Chandler, Jeff (Box A-23, Folder 102)
    - Chandler, Len (Box A-23, Folder 103)
    - Chandler, Roland (Box A-23, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: Lou Manna
    - Chandler, Stanley L. (Box A-23, Folder 105)
    - Chandler, Dr. Zala (Box A-23, Folder 106)
    - Chandran, Joshua R. (Dr.) (Box A-23, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: Office of Public Information, Union Theological Seminary
    - Chaney, Anne (Box A-23, Folder 108)
      Photographer if identified: Billie Billing
    - Chaney, Fanny (Box A-23, Folder 109)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, United Press International, Frederick H. Simmons, Alvin J. Burley
    - Chaney, Lon (Box A-23, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: Sherm Scott
    - Chaney, William R. (Box A-23, Folder 111)
    - Change (Box A-23, Folder 112)
    - "Changes" (Box A-23, Folder 113)
    - Chantels, The (Box A-23, Folder 114)
    - Chanticleer, Raven (Box A-23, Folder 115)
      Also 3 velox prints and multiple typescript press releases. One press release is signed by Chanticleer.
      Photographer if identified: Joseph Ratke, Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Chapin, Arthur H. (Box A-23, Folder 116)
    - Chaplin, Mrs. Bernice (Box A-23, Folder 117)
    - Chaplin, Joe Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-23, Folder 118)
    - Chaplin, Mildred D. (Box A-23, Folder 119)
    - Chapman, Alice (Box A-23, Folder 120)
    - Chapman, Bill (Box A-23, Folder 121)
    - Chapman, Donald (Box A-23, Folder 122)
    - Chapman, Earl (Box A-23, Folder 123)
    - Chapman, Frank (Box A-23, Folder 124)
    - Chapman, Freida (Box A-23, Folder 125)
    - Chapman, Harold (Box A-23, Folder 126)
    - Chapman, Helen (Box A-23, Folder 127)
    - Chapman, Leonard Rev. (see Rev. Sterling Carey) (Box A-23, Folder 128)
    - Chapman, Lori (Box A-23, Folder 129)
    - Chapman, Raymond (Box A-23, Folder 130)
    - Chapman, Robert (Father) (Box A-23, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Ed Bagwell
    - Chapman, Robert Campbell Rev. (Box A-23, Folder 132)
    - Chapman, Ronald W. (Box A-23, Folder 133)
    - Chapman, Ronnie (Box A-23, Folder 134)
    - Chapman, Samuel O. Jr. (Box A-23, Folder 135)
      1 typescript leaf (press release).
    - Chappel, Emma (Box A-23, Folder 136)
    - Chappell, Florence H. (Box A-23, Folder 137)
      Print is stapled to a leaf of paper.
    - Chappell, Lillian (Box A-23, Folder 138)
    - Chappelle, Shirley (Box A-23, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Cecil Layne
    - The Chaps (Box A-23, Folder 140)
    - Charisma (Box A-23, Folder 141)
    - Charity, Elaine (Box A-23, Folder 142)
    - Charity Club (Box A-23, Folder 143)
    - Charles, Bernard (Box A-23, Folder 144)
      Also 2 velox prints. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. Also multiple press releases.
      Photographer if identified: Bachrach, B&G International Photos, Martin Helfer, Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Charles, Bernie (Box A-23, Folder 145)
    - Charles, Clemard J. (Box A-23, Folder 146)
    - Charles, Ed (Box A-23, Folder 147)
    - Charles, Ezzard (Box A-23, Folder 148)
    - Charles' Gallery (Box A-23, Folder 149)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bill Stone,
    - Charles, Gerald (Box A-23, Folder 150)
    - The Charles H. Fellows for 1984-85 (Box A-23, Folder 151)
    - Charles, Honey (Box A-23, Folder 152)
    - Charles, Mary (Box A-23, Folder 153)
    - King Charles Troupe (Box A-23, Folder 154)
    - Charles, Lauriette Cecile (Box A-23, Folder 155)
    - Charles, Morris (Box A-23, Folder 156)
      Press release from Dept. of the Navy (Charles was a POW).
      Photographer if identified: US Navy
    - Charles, Norman (Box A-23, Folder 157)
    - Charles, Pearnel (Box A-23, Folder 158)
    - Charles, Pepsi (Box A-23, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Cleveland Davies
    - Charles, Ray (Box A-23, Folder 160)
      One print is stapled to a single-leaf press release. One print is accompanied by a two-leaf press release with tape (detached). One set of two prints is attached to single-leaf carbonscript press release from the Original Hebrew Israelite Nation.
    - Charles, Ray (Box A-23, Folder 161)
      Also one computer-printed draft of a press release dated Jan. 1980 (3 leaves), 3 velox prints, and one halftone print of artwork by Geo. Lee.
    - Charles, Ray (Box A-23, Folder 162)
    - Charles, Raymond (Box A-23, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Charleston, Robt. (Box A-23, Folder 164)
    - Charles, Suzette (Box A-23, Folder 165)
      Photographer if identified: John Tannock, Curt Clemons
    - Charles Unicycle Riders (Box A-23, Folder 166)
    - Charleton, Bridgette (Box A-23, Folder 167)
    - Charlie & Ray (Box A-23, Folder 168)
    - Charlton, Jack (Box A-23, Folder 169)
    - Charlton, Jeff (Box A-23, Folder 170)
      Also one velox and one offset-printed images.
    - Charlton, Philip (Box A-23, Folder 171)
    - Charlot, Laure (Box A-23, Folder 172)
    - Charlot, Father Lucien (Box A-23, Folder 173)
    - The Charms (Box A-23, Folder 174)
    - Chase, Allison (Box A-23, Folder 175)
    - Chase, Bill (Box A-23, Folder 176)
    - Chase, Elizabeth (Box A-23, Folder 177)
    - Chase, Gordon (Box A-23, Folder 178)
      Press release attached to print with paper clip.
    - Chase, Juanita (Box A-23, Folder 179)
    - Chase, Lillian (Box A-23, Folder 180)
    - Chase, Nancy Mrs. (Box A-23, Folder 181)
    - Chase, Thomas (Box A-23, Folder 182)
    - Barbara Chase-Riboud (Box A-23, Folder 183)
    - Chatman, Don (Box A-23, Folder 184)
    - Chatman, Robert (Box A-23, Folder 185)
    - Chatti, Meimoun (Box A-23, Folder 186)
    - Chauncey, Harrell (Box A-23, Folder 187)
    - Chauncey, Anthony (Box A-23, Folder 188)
    - Chavers, Norvlean (Box A-23, Folder 189)
    - Chavez, Cesar (Box A-23, Folder 190)
      Press release from St. John's University.